<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GreenGuide</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string-array name="guidelines_array">
        <item>Guidelines</item>
        <item>\nIntroduction to LoveGreenGuide\n</item>
        <item>China is famous for Confucianism which was long the basis for ruling the country.
            Through thousands of years under this moral system, we accomplished tremendous
            achievements and accumulated many cultural treasures. But as time has gone by, we’ve
            started to lose the senses of virtue and morality, and economic development has
            contributed to a loss of public spirit and responsibility.\n\n
            As descendants of the Yandi and Huangdi emperors, we burden the responsibility to bring
            back the moral and cultural treasures we used to have. “LoveGreenGuide” connects the
            impact of reputation and rewards with morality through the assistance of modern
            technology. It helps to restrain poor behavior by inviting the public’s assistance.
            \n</item>
        <item>\n<b>Dear members:</b>\n\n
            Welcome to the “LoveGreenGuide” family. First, accept our deep appreciation for joining
            us to improve the environment. Your help increases our strength and adds confidence to
            our path forward.\n</item>
        <item>\nLoveGreenGuide Member Trust Agreement\n</item>
        <item>The sole purpose of this website is to provide an information-communication platform.
            Users can register with their email and post comments. To protect the user’s information
            security, we ensure that:\n\n
            <b>1. We will take users’ personal information (including account, email and comments)
            as our priority to protect.\n\n
            2. All information filled by users will protected by the company.\n\n
            3. The company will list the full and detailed process of collecting and securing
            information to ensure the safety of users’ information. \n\n
            4. We will make a set of rules restricting access to information and limiting the number
            of employees able to access the user’s information.\n\n
            5. If a user violates Chinese laws, we will provide the information under the legal
            process only within the requirements of the laws and the judicial authority. All these
            procedures must be taken in accordance with the appropriate official and lawful
            documents and legal method. We will do our best to protect users’ personal
            information.\n\n
            6. We will never provide users’ information to any unofficial government or non-judicial
                authority organization or person.\n</b></item>
        <item>\nAbout Personal Information Security\n</item>
        <item><b>Summary:</b>\n\n
            Our purpose is to build a website with credibility and trust. We will
            ensure the accuracy of the website and protect the rights for all users, employees and
            related companies.\n\n
            This is an unofficial independent website and we appreciate your joining. If you have
            information about a serious environmental or illegal incident, please contact the police
            department immediately. Meanwhile, you are also welcome to post the incident on our
            website.\n\n
            If any content in this agreement conflicts with Chinese laws, we take the Chinese laws
            as the standard.\n\n
            <b>Details:</b>\n\n
            As a member of LoveGreenGuide, I promise to:\n\n
            <b>1. Maintain the high quality and accuracy of the website, and affirm that trust
            comes first.\n\n
            2. Refuse to be involved in any untruthful comment activity and contact the website if
            I see any untruthful information.\n\n
            3. Follow all laws relate to information security.\n\n
            4. Not be involved in any illegal activity.\n\n</b>
            As a member of LoveGreenGuide, I promise <b>not</b> to partake in:\n\n
            <b>1. Any activity which involves untruthful comments for the purpose of profit.\n\n
            2. Any aggressive or illegal activity on the website.\n\n
            3. Any activity that impacts the accuracy, fairness and order of the website.\n\n</b>
            Please maintain the accuracy of the website and to keep this site a pure and truthful
            information exchange platform.\n\n
            If we find any disallowed actions, we will respond on the basis of the information
            available to us and our investigation. We will punish anyone who violates the laws and
            our policies as follows:\n\n
            <b>1. Delete comments in question and send out a warning to related persons.\n\n
            2. Delete all comments and pictures by the user and lower the credit level of the
            account.\n\n
            3. For users who are involved, their account will be marked with a sign saying “has
            published untruthful comments”. The time period for this posting will be determined by
            us.\n\n
            4. Repeated disallowed actions and activities will cause us to close the account
            permanently.\n\n</b>
            Addition: If the disallowed activity (comments or pictures) violates Chinese laws, we
            will hand over to the police department and related company as evidence. All of these
            will be done only under legal methods.\n\n
            Just as a beautiful and harmonious society is created together, our website also depends
            on your participation. We appreciate your joining and hope for your help to maintain the
            accuracy of this website!\n\n
            All of the above is adopted on Oct 12, 2015 and effective immediately.\n\n
            All members will obey the agreements above from this moment.\n\n
            This agreement is provided in Chinese and English. The Chinese version is the
            authority.\n</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="about_array">
        <item>About Us</item>
        <item>Join Us</item>
        <item>Contact Us</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="industry_prompt">Industry</string>

    <string-array name="industry_array">
        <item>Advanced Electronics</item>
        <item>Aerospace \&amp; Defense</item>
        <item>Automotive \&amp; Assembly</item>
        <item>Retail banking</item>
        <item>Food and beverages</item>
        <item>Consumables</item>
        <item>Toys \&amp; electronics</item>
        <item>Apparel</item>
        <item>Grocery</item>
        <item>Building materials</item>
        <item>Basic Materials</item>
        <item>Chemicals \&amp; Agriculture</item>
        <item>EPNG (Electric Power \&amp; Natural gas)</item>
        <item>Oil \&amp; Gas</item>
        <item>Pharma</item>
        <item>Medical products</item>
        <item>High Tech</item>
        <item>Media \&amp; Entertainment</item>
        <item>Telecom</item>
        <item>Semiconductors</item>
        <item>Utility/ESCo (Energy Service Company)</item>
        <item>Retailer</item>
        <item>Portfolio company</item>
        <item>Hotel</item>
        <item>Waste management</item>
        <item>NGO</item>
        <item>Government</item>
        <item>Storage</item>
        <item>Airline</item>
        <item>Paper and Pulp</item>
        <item>Networking equipment and services</item>

    </string-array>
</resources>